<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pepper Mills</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/meetings/peppermills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/meetings/peppermills/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Presenter For February:&#xA;Stephen J Cook&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stephen is the owner and proprietor of Coastal Wood Design (coastalwooddesgn.com) and does woodturning, Historical Windows, Custom Wooden Countertops, Cabinets, and Furniture.&#xA;The Club had its second meeting for 2024 on the morning of Saturday 17 February as scheduled.  There were 19 club members in attendance, and all watched as our presenter Stephen J. Cook demonstrated how to turn and assemble pepper mills. Everyone enjoyed the demonstration and learned a lot of new Woodturning technique s they pertain to Pepper Mills. Come join us for our next meeting on the 16 March 2024 at 09:00 AM. This March meeting will be held at a members residence so look later for details on how to get there&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Sided Box With a Lid</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/meetings/threesidedboxwithlid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/meetings/threesidedboxwithlid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Presenter For January:&#xA;Dr. Evan Bahr&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Club had its first meeting for 2024 on a very cold and blustery day in east central Georgia. There were 14 club members in attendance and all watched as our presenter Dr. Evan Bahr demonstrated how to turn three sided boxes with matching lids. Everyone enjoyed the demonstration and learned a few new turning techniques. Come join us for our next meeting on the 17th of February 2024 at 09:00 AM.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
